[Music]
ch
ch baby
[Music]
stuck in his
way walking with his chest
out knows what he
a but don't know what to be
about he
[Music]
understand could be better
that he could move
[Music]
mountains and be a
do in the promised
land I can't hold his
hand and make him
comprehend that it's all his for the Tak
idiots and exons frauds and miss me to
refusing to believe that she the company
keep talking get it together got to get
right how you expecting things to change
when you ain't changing your life
leaning on your team but they subers no
follow through a hustle they steady
missing layups you rely on working out
to get your we up but they be posted on
the BL think up he don't see it but he's
aware of the world comprehens some of
the scope and the oppression in it but
he don't get that though his boys are is
fam though they'll run guns blazing when
the is the fan our Manchild pissing
on the promised land only seeds planted
in the womb of a woman I know you need
your man's and them to have your back
but you know and I know they also hold
you
back in the promised
land I can't hold his
hand and make him come
that it's all his for the Tak and I
can't change him I can't change him no I
can't blame him I can't blame
him I know where he's
from and how hard it is to let
go oh w what you
[Music]
know ch ch
[Applause]
[Music]
ch a chain of
fool yeah ch ch
[Applause]
ch he's in the chain of
[Music]
all